Sorry. I’ll tell you how it’s to be done, you see.
很抱歉，我會告訴你該怎樣做，你看
Now all right?
現在可以嗎？
You have to go from forward backwards,
你要從前面往後
otherwise the hairs start coming forward.
不然，頭髲會向前
Is it all right for you people?
這樣可以嗎？
Just hold it.
只拿著它
This is rather a big one, you see, just –
這很大，你看，只是…
just a minute, I’ll take it.
只一會兒，我拿著它
Hold it, eh? I’ll just put it right. Just hold it.
拿著它，呀？我只是弄好它，只拿著它
In Krishna’s – this is Krishna’s country, you see,
在克里希納的…這是克里希納的國家
and it has to be everything upside-down.
一切都必須本末倒置
All right. Big problem!
好吧，大問題！
Now let Me see.
現在讓我看看
Now it’s better.
現在好一點
Yes, it’s better idea.
對，這是好主意
Put it that way.
這樣放它
I look like a
我像一個
Red Indian lady;
印第安女士
Inca, Inca-style.
印加，印加款式
All right?
對嗎？
Both hands.
雙手
Somebody should take a full photograph.
有人應該拍一張整體的照片
I hope you get some miraculous photographs.
我希望你能拍到奇蹟的照片
Aarti …[Marathi]
搖燈禮…(馬拉地語)
Just give the bandhan there.
只要做班丹
Kundalini’s just clearcut.
靈量是很清晰的
No, anti-clockwise.
不，反時針方向
No, no, there, at ….
不，不，這裡，在…
Just bow down. Let’s see.
只要跪下，請我們看看
Keep bowing down. We want to see your kundalini.
保持跪下，我們想看你的靈量
It’s all right. Now you try on him. Just move it.
好吧，現在試試他，只移動它
Swadisthan.
腹輪
Center Heart.
心輪中部
So hold it tight, hold it.
拿緊它，拿著它
He’s all right.
他沒問題
You just see his kundalini, at Nabhi.
你只看他的靈量，在臍輪
Just bow down. Is he all right?
只跪下，他還好嗎？
Left Swadisthan and the Nabhi. You come now.
左臍輪和臍輪，你現在來
Bandhan there. Now you are all right. You are all right.
這裡做班丹，你現在沒問題，你沒問題
Everybody. Let us see everybody. It’s better to watch it.
每一個人，讓我們看每一個人，最好看著它
You come along just one minute.
你來吧，只一分鐘
I want to see everybody’s kundalini. Now, it’s good.
我想看每一個人的靈量，現在，很好
Now Doug, you are all right. You are all right.
現在德，你沒事吧，你沒事
But in the Vishuddhi, throat, little bit.
但在喉輪，在喉嚨，一點點
All right, now, let’s see, one by one.
好吧，現在，讓我看看，一個接一個
Now just put both the hands forward.
現在把雙手向前
Just see, his kundalini.
只看看，他的靈量
Come along. See, his vibrations.
來吧，看，他的生命能量
Ah. All right?
呀！好吧？
No, left – not all right. We’ll see, now.
不，左邊，不妥當，我們會看，現在
Michael.
米高
Hold your breath. Hold your breath. Hmm.
忍著呼吸，忍著呼吸，
Leave it.
放鬆呼吸
Ah. Nabhi.
呀，臍輪
All right?
好吧？
Are you all right?
你沒事吧？
Let’s see. Started now.
讓我們看看，現在開始
You are perfectionists, all of you!
你是追求完美主義者，你們全部人
He himself is a perfectionist.
他是追求完美主義者
Heart.
心
Done! Been worried a bit too much.
完成了，過分憂心
Nothing to worry. It’s done now, all right?
沒甚麽要擔憂，完成了，好吧？
She’s all right, now. She’s all right.
她沒事，現在，她沒事
Are you all right? Why?
你沒事嗎？為甚麽？
Hold it, hold it there. Hold your breath for a minute.
忍著，忍著，忍著呼吸一會兒
Leave it now ….
現在放鬆呼吸…
You come here. This lady.
你來這裡，這個女士
Yes, you come here.
是，你來這裡
She’s catching on the center Heart. Now, hold it .
她的心輪中部有阻塞，現在拿著它
… Sit down, sit down. Now, bow.
坐下，坐下，現在跪下
Hah! Leave it.
哈！於鬆
Center Heart …
心輪中部…
Void … She went to some gurus?
幻海…她到過一些導師？
You have been?
你到過？
…. I don’t know what is it ….
我不知道是甚麽…
What is it? ….
是甚麽？
Builders of the ….
某種建築者
Center Heart you are catching.
你的心輪中部有阻塞
Hold your breath, please.
忍著呼吸
You leave it.
放鬆呼吸
Again hold your breath.
再次忍著呼吸
Hah! Leave it.
哈！放鬆呼吸
Are you better now?
你現在好點嗎？
How are you?
你好嗎？
Left Agnya.
左額輪
You’re all right.
你沒事
Is she all right? See her vibrations.
她妥當嗎，看看她的生命能量
She has to work it out on her left.
她要清潔她的左邊
Left is problem, I think.
問題在左邊，我認為
Center Heart [Marathi]
心輪中部(馬拉地語)
Ah! Now it’s good
呀！現在很好
… Now. All right.
現在，好吧…
Have you got one like that? Smaller one?
你有沒有拿到像這個的？小的？
… Are you all right now?
你沒事嗎？
You got caught up with others.
你受別人感染
Don’t get worried. Nothing to worry.
不要擔憂，沒甚麽要擔憂
First class!
一流！
Put your right hand towards that. That’s right.
把右手向著這裡，就這樣
And left hand towards Me. Now.
左手向著我，現在
Why do you hear so many things? Just now take it …
為甚麽你聽到那麽多事情？現在只要拿它…
Very good, excellent.
很好，一流
Tell her how to do it.
告訴她該怎樣做
Little this side.
這裡一點點
You tell her, little this side.
你告訴她，這面一點
Put it, hah ….
放它，呀…
Left Nabhi.
左臍輪
How is he? ….
他怎麽了？
left Swadisthan
左腹輪
Better?
好一點嗎？
How many days you did that?
你做了多少天？
Not for a long time?
時間不長？
About how many years?
大約多少年？
Put it next to the light. Higher. Fixing the light there.
把它放在光的附近，高點，把光定下
In between, you have to hold your breath.
在之間，你要忍著呼吸
[Marathi]
(馬拉地語)
Ah! Good.
呀，好
You’re all right now.
你現在沒事
All right?
對嗎？
What happens in Vancouver?
溫哥華發生了甚麽？
Must meditate regularly, that’s the real way.
要經常靜坐，這才是真正的途徑
Now, let’s see ….
現在，讓我們看看…
Patricia.
帕
She’s from a very strict ashram
她是從一個很嚴格的靜室來的
– of Bala the great!
偉大的Bala！
You are perfectly all right. You are all right.
你完全沒問題，你沒事
No problem.
沒問題
Bala is coming here, like Hanumana,
Bala會來這裡，像哈奴曼，bala
to America very soon.
很快來美國
But you see, when he starts all correcting and all that
但你看，當他開始糾正
he’s all right, but then sometimes he gets so tired,
他沒事，但有時他會很疲倦
then he becomes a complaint master, you know – isn’t he?
他便會變成投訴專家，你知道，他是嗎？
So I have told him next time
所以我已經告訴他下一次
you don’t complain to Me about anyone,
你不要向我投訴任何人
otherwise he’ll get ….
不然他會得…
… is done. All right, he’s done. Excellent!
已經完成了，好吧，完成了，很棒！
You are right, all right, come along.
你對，好吧，來吧
You are perfectly all right. Yes, now come along.
你完全沒事，對，現在來吧
If you want Me to see you again, on hand.
若你想我再見你，在手上
You are perfectly all right.
你完全沒事
Very good.
很好
For trade you have to now stick onto your job, all right?
你要貼附著你的工作，好吧？
It goes from right to left, right to left
它從右到左，右到左
– that’s not good, eh?
這不好，呀？
Just try My trade!
只要嘗試我的手藝
May God bless you.
願神祝福你
I think, you’ll be all right.
我想，你會沒事
But you see, your Heart catching, all that is because,
但你看，你的心輪阻塞，全因為
if you start changing jobs,
若你開始轉換工作
it works on your – put your hands towards Me.
它在你身上運作，把你的雙手向著我
You are all right, James, and despite Santa Cruz!
你沒事，占士，雖然在聖克魯茲(美國加州)！
May God bless you.
願神祝福你們
I’m really very happy about it.
我真的很高興
I didn’t know you worked there in Santa Cruz.
我不知道你在聖克魯茲工作
That’s something I’m very much worried about.
這是我很擔心的
May God bless you.
願神祝福你
I’m very happy that you are there.
我很高興你在這裡
Something is working out.
有些事情在成就
It’s good. You are very good.
很好，你很好
Santa Cruz otherwise could be –
聖克魯茲不然會…
[Yogi: I should stay in Santa Cruz?]
(瑜伽士︰我要留在聖克魯茲？)
Yes, I think so, you can.
對，我認為是，你可以
Very few people can, without catching,
很少人能，沒有阻塞
so you’d better stay there.
所以你最好留在哪裡
So may God bless you.
願神祝福你
Now, who else? So everybody has been?
現在，還有誰？每個人都已經做了？
Very good. Excellent .…
很好，很棒
Now. Better take out the … if you can.
現在，最好拿…若你可以
It’s mine, all right, take it out, doesn’t matter.
這是我的，好吧，把它拿出來，不要緊
Better?
好一點？
That’s how you can treat people, you see?
你就是要這樣對待人，你明白嗎？
Ah, now. Left …
呀，現在，左…
left Nabhi, left Nabhi.
左臍輪，左臍輪
You are all right.
你沒事
Hah, now, better? Better.
哈，現在，好一點？
[Yogini: Should I not wear the other rings?]
(女瑜伽士︰我是不是不要穿上另一個介子？)
Better not, because sometimes your chakras
最好不，因為你的輪穴有時
are not all right.
會不妥當
They give a pressure ….
他們給壓力…
What?
甚麽？
Yes, that’s what is needed.
是，這就是需要的
Who else? Come along, come.
還有誰？來吧，來
Nabhi … Swadisthana …
臍輪…腹輪…
artistic?
富藝術感
Hah! It’s all right.
哈！會沒事
Working in the restaurant, so you can have …!
在餐廳工作，所以你可以
She’s all right.
她沒事
Come along now, who else?
現在來吧，還有誰？
Ah, better, isn’t it?
呀，好一點，是嗎？
I’m saying that you search a husband for her;
我是說你為她找丈夫
because I searched yours in no time!
因為我很快為你找到丈夫
It was such a fast thing, such a fast thing, wasn’t it?
這是很快，很快，是嗎？
Those who tie it up put their hands like that.
那些繫上它的人把手像這樣放
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah!
嘩、嘩、嘩、嘩、嘩！
I think you just take a photograph.
我想你剛拍下照片
So, Alex, everybody has got it? Come forward.
所以，阿力，每個人都拿到它？上前來
Let’s see. Are you all right now?
讓我看看，你沒事嗎？
Better? Better now.
好一點？現在好一點
Let it work out. That’s all right.
讓它成就，這會沒事
Hah, now, is he? Left.
哈，現在，是他嗎？左邊
Right to the left. Right to the left.
從右到左，從右到左
Ah, that’s it.
呀，就是它
Hah! Done!
哈！完成了
All right?
好吧？
How is he? Bring him.
他怎麽了？帶他來
Where’s the other baby?
另一個嬰兒在哪裡？
Where is he? Shaun.
他在哪裡？姍
Shaun, come here.
姍，來這裡
I wanted you to come and make Me wear this.
我想你來幫我穿上這個
You have to make – good, you’re all right now.
你要…好，你現在好吧
God bless you – now, now, Shaun,
願神祝福你，現在，現在，姍
you have to put this in My neck;
你要把這個放在我的頸上
she’s feeling shy, you see.
她害羞，你看
Now, this one is not feeling shy.
現在，這個不害羞
Now, let Me have this one.
現在，讓這個來
This one doesn’t feel shy.
這個不害羞
Ohoho!
噢！
Oh! You are crying, so he’s also crying!
噢！你在哭，他也在哭
He’s also …
他也…
See now, they have done the puja,
看看現在，他們已經做了崇拜
they have done everything for Me, you have done nothing!
他們為我做一切，你甚麽也沒做
Shaun, you have to put some – All right,
姍，你要把一些…好吧
let’s – don’t disturb her, they are all sleeping.
讓…不要騷擾她，他們全睡著了
[Yogini asks about a name given previously to her child]
(女瑜伽士詢問有關之前為她孩子命名的事情)
You put it “Narasimha”, should be her name.
你用“Narasimha”, 這個應是她的名字
Where was that?
那是甚麽？
Narasimhini.
Narasimhini.
I gave you the name!
我給你的名字！
She was born – when was she born?
她出世了，她甚麽時候出生
[Yogini: On July the fifth.]
(女瑜伽士︰7月5日)
Ah, that’s why, because she’s a Leo.
呀，就是這原因，因為她是獅子座
You can give her another name also, a simple one.
你可以給她另一個名字，一個簡單的名字
That’s a power of Goddess, you know.
這是女神的力量，你知道
Oh! Somebody’s coming up! Ah!
噢！有人上來！呀！
You can call her Kesar. Kesar.
你可以稱呼她為Kesar
“Kesar” means “the power of the lion.”
“Kesar” 意思是獅子的力量
Kesar. “Kesari” is the lion,
Kesar. “Kesari”是獅子
and the “Kesar” is the power of the lion;
“Kesar” 是獅子的力量
same thing as Narasimha.
與Narasimha是一樣的
That’s easier, Kesar.
這個較容易， Kesar.
What does she want? K-E-S-A-R. Kesar.
她想要甚麽？K-E-S-A-R. Kesar.
All right.
好吧
He wants to have something more.
他想要多一點
Whatever you want, Shaun, what do you want?
無論你想要甚麽，姍，你想要甚麽？
Shaun, what do you want to have? You want to have this?
姍，你想要甚麽？你想要這個？
Which one do you want to eat?
你想吃那一個？
Which one you like? You’re hungry. Whatever it is, have it.
你喜歡那一個？你餓了，無論怎樣，拿吧
Everybody has been? Hallo.
每個人都已經有？喂
Come along, come along. What do you want?
來吧，來吧，你想要甚麽？
All right, all right. Let him have something there.
好吧，好吧，讓他拿這裡的
They all like grapes.
他們都喜歡葡萄
There. So let’s see you. You have to bow.
這裡，讓我看看，你要跪下
You – she has to still come, yes.
你…她仍要來，對…
What about you? You have, I see.
你又怎樣？你有，我明白
So sweet.
很甜
He’s shy, that’s all. He’s excellent, Shaun is excellent!
他害羞，就這樣，他很棒，姍很棒
Very beautiful, excellent, see now!
很漂亮，很棒，看現在！
Now slowly open the eyes. He’s a bit shy.
現在慢慢張開眼睛，他有點害羞
[Yogis: Butter.]
(瑜伽士︰牛油)
You made it? You made it here?
你造的？你在這裡造的？
Really? It’s great!
真的？很了不起！
Now, take it, it’s all right. Good. May God bless you.
現在，拿它，不要緊，好，願神祝福你
Come along, now let Me see.
來吧，現在讓我看看
Are you all right now? Not yet?
你還好嗎？還未？
I think you sit more comfortably.
我想你坐得更舒適
You’re very tired.
你真的很倦
Be comfortable, that’s important. And now let’s see.
舒適點，這很重要，現在讓我看看
What’s the matter? His left side is so tired today.
有甚麽事？他的左邊今天是那麽倦
Left Agnya is still there.
左額輪仍在這裡
And right Swadisthana, Heart … chakras.
右腹輪，心…輪穴
Now come along.
現在來吧
David, you put this light on his back.
大偉，你把這火放在他的背後
Here. And now you put both your hands towards Me like this.
這裡，現在你像這樣把雙手向著我
The light you take it in your hand, that one, that one.
把火拿在手裡，這個，這個
The one that is before you.
那個在你面前的
Now, she’s all right. She’s all right.
現在，她沒事，她會沒事
You’re all right. May God bless you.
你沒事，願神祝福你
You are all right. Now, who else is left?
你沒事，現在，還有誰？
In Marathi also we say “I” is “me”, “I”.
馬拉地語我們也說"I" 即「我」
Better? Now – it will work out.
好一點？現在，它會解決
[Yogi: Shri Lalita.]
(瑜伽士︰Shri Lalita.)
It’s catching.
它有阻塞
Put right hand on the Mother Earth.
把右手放在大地之母上
Hah! She’s all right. You are all right. May God bless you.
哈！她沒事，你也沒事，願神祝福你
Come.
來
Now you grow up fast;
你成長得很快
you have to give realization!
你要給自覺！
Hah! All right. She’s all right.
哈！好吧，她沒事
You are all right.
你沒事
You come along now. You have been.
你現在來，你已經
All of you? Now, right.
你們全部人？現在，右
Heart.
心
Right Swadisthan.
右腹輪
Left Swadisthan.
左腹輪
Heart.
心
Both sides.
兩面
Combination is funny – left, right Swadisthan and Heart;
混合是很有趣的---左，右腹輪和心輪
center Heart now.
現在心輪中部
[Marathi]
(馬拉地語)
Hah!
哈！
Hold your breath.
忍著呼吸
Do like that, do like that.
像這樣做
Hah! Better?
哈！好一點？
Better now.
現在好一點
Better, but she has to work.
好一點，她要清潔
Hallo!
喂！
Work it out, because a funny combination:
把它清潔，因為是個有趣的組合
left Swadisthan, right Swadisthan, Heart, and Sahasrara.
左腹輪，右腹輪，心輪和頂輪
E-G-O.
自我
As simple as that.
就是這樣簡單
Rub My foot, right? Still.
擦我的腳，對，仍然
Now, what you do is to put your right hand towards Me,
現在，把右手向著我
left hand up. Let’s see, one by one.
左手向上，讓我看看，一個接一個
Are you better now?
你好一點嗎？
Still the left is catching.
左邊仍有阻塞
Why don’t you both get some lemon and chillies?
你們兩個為何不拿些檸檬和辣椒？
Would be a good idea.
這會是個好主意
What have you been doing?
你在做甚麽？
Have you been – I don’t know what you have been doing.
你有否…我不知道你做了些甚麽
I just don’t understand.
我只是不明白
You had right side, but this left you didn’t have it.
你偏右脈，但這左脈你沒有
Left Nabhi.
左臍輪
Very hectic liver.
很熱的肝
That way you’re much better.
這樣你會好點
Left Nabhi’s all right, but left Swadisthana.
左臍輪還好，但左腹輪
That is your psychology.
這是你的心理
Do you meditate?
你有沒有靜坐？
You see, I just thought that right-sidedness
你看，我只是想到右邊
could be down in a place where it is quieter,
可以下降到一處較安靜的地方
so that your speed at least should come down first of all.
那麽你的速度最少先減慢
And then it will be all right.
它便會妥當
Just put down your speed.
只要放慢速度
“I don’t do anything,” you should say.
你應說︰「我甚麽也沒做。」
All right? Put it everything into the hands of God.
對嗎？把一切交托在神的手裡
Still there?
仍有阻塞？
Better now.
現在好點
It’s very surprising.
這是很令人驚訝
What’s that? A gift? That’s all right. Thank you.
這是甚麽？禮物？好吧，謝謝
What’s this – two? Two things not allowed!
這是甚麽---兩件？不容許兩件
What’s that?
這是甚麽？
I did not see the gift!
我看不到禮物！
That is his trick, I tell you: I was buying it, and he bought it!
這是他的把戲，我告訴你︰我買這個，他買這個
Oh, it’s beautiful. So we quarreled for quite some time.
噢！很漂亮，我們爭吵了一會兒
It’s not easy to win over Mr. Danny!
要勝過丹尼先生是不容易
But this one is a trick you played.
這是你玩的把戲
This one is, this is not. This one was tricky.
這個是，這個不是，這個很微妙
For the other two is all right, but this one was tricky.
其他兩個還好，這個很微妙
It’s a beautiful piece, though, isn’t it?
這個很美麗，是嗎？
These are magnets?
它們是有吸引力
Beautiful. Very good.
很漂亮，很好
We should get a suitcase
我們要拿一個箱子
where you can keep all these things, in several boxes.
來盛載這些東西，要幾個箱子
You see, in that if you put this ….
你看，若你把這個放在…
No, he was saying, doctor was saying he has got a box
不，他在說，醫生說他要拿一個箱子來
which he’ll vacate it.
他要把它空出
But so far they have not telephoned, these people.
但到現在他們還未有致電給這些人
Ah, he is worried on that.
呀，他擔憂著這些事情
All right now. Better? Are you better?
現在沒事，好一點？你好一點嗎？
I think first the financial situation should improve,
我想財政狀況首先改善
then you’ll be all right.
那麽你便沒事
I think if you really go to Mexico,
我想若你真的到墨西哥
that would make some money also.
也會賺到點錢
And she is also very clever.
她也是很聰明
May God bless you.
願神祝福你
But to establish, how will they do it, suddenly?
但要鞏固，他們怎能做到，忽然地？
They have to ask the government here
他們要問這裡的政府
to employ them, or something.
顧用他們
But there is no job problem there.
但這裡沒有就業的問題
All right.
好吧
That’s a good idea. May God bless you.
這是個好主意，願神祝福你
I don’t know how also his boss is.
我不知道他的老闆怎麽樣
Might be he’s caught up with his boss, or something.
或許他和他的老闆都有阻塞
How is he? [Yogi: Terrible, Mother.]
他怎麽了？(瑜伽士︰母親，很可怕)
Ah, that’s it. [Yogi: Garam’s uncle.]
呀，就是這樣。(瑜伽士︰嘉的叔叔)
Because you are not so bad. I know. I heard.
因為你們並不那麽壞，我知道，我聽到
Must be, must be him.
一定是，一定是他
So better change him now.
所以現在最好換了他
As he says, they can find out something for you.
就如他所說，他們能為你找到一些東西
Better try.
最好試試吧
Because that will bring down her speed also, I think,
因為這樣也能把她的速度減慢，我認為
because your country is very, moving slowly, yes.
因為你的國家是很…移動得很慢，對
It’s a very speedy place also;
這也是很急速的地方
America’s extremely speedy.
美國是極之急速
Those who have no speed can come here,
那些缺乏速度的人可以來這裡
but those who have speed should get out of this place.
但那些快速的人則要離開
At first I thought it would be nice if you go to New York,
我先以為若你到紐約會很好
but New York is no less, and that won’t suit.
但紐約並沒有慢下來，這不適合你
So if it could be arranged in Mexico, nothing like.
所以若可以安排在墨西哥，無可比擬
Once they are all right then there’s no problem,
一旦他們妥當，便沒有任何問題
once they are balanced; but both are caught up.
一旦他們平衡。但他們兩個卻受感染，
And they are good people there, they’re nice,
他們是好人，很好的人
they’re not horrible people in that country.
在這國家，他們不是可怕的人
Except for this black magic they do,
除了他們的巫術
which can be corrected.
但這是能糾正的
Slowly they’ll be all right.
他們慢慢會妥當
Things are so much cheaper there, so much cheaper ….
這裡的東西是那麽便宜，那麽便宜
Handmade, yes, that’s also a good thing,
人手造的，對，這也是好東西
compared to machinery.
與機器相比
So all right, thank you very much. May God bless you.
所以好吧，很感謝你們，願神祝福你
Thank you for the purse. May God bless you.
謝謝你的錢包，願神祝福你
Now as you have given Me purse,
因為你給我錢包
you must have lots of money here!
你在這裡必定有很多錢！
In this ashram you must get lots of money.
在這個集體靜室，你必定取得很多錢
So far, nobody gave Me a purse, for your information.
到目前為止，沒有人給我錢包，我告訴你
This is the first time.
這是第一次
[Yogi: For auspiciousness we should have put a dollar in.]
(瑜伽士︰為祥瑞的原因，我們要放一個錢幣在內)
Ah, it’s a good idea – one dollar, then.
呀，好主意，一個錢幣
Five dollar is too much. One dollar.
五元太多，一元吧
No, no, no, no. This is the puja money?
不，不，不，不，這是崇拜的錢？
So this you give it in the general puja there,
這個是你在這裡一般的崇拜給的
when they have it, eh?
他們何時拿到它，呀？
Now I have got this purse, that’s all.
現在我拿到這個錢包，就這樣
You don’t have one dollar, isn’t it?
你沒有一元錢幣，是嗎？
All right.
好吧
But he’s given twenty-one now.
但他給了二十一
He’s another difficult person!
他是另一個難應付的人！
All right. Now what I’m saying,
好吧，現在我要說
that this puja money whatever you’ve got,
這些崇拜的錢
you count it and put it in a packet,
你要數算它，把它放在袋裡
give it to Me in the general puja money,
把一般崇拜的錢給我
but from your side – all right?
在你旁邊，對嗎？
So for the real puja it’s going to be there.
對真正的崇拜，它會在這裡
It’s of course a real puja too, today, it was a great puja,
這個當然是真的崇拜，今天，是個很了不起的崇拜
but the Krishna Puja we are going to have there.
我們會在那裡舉行克里希納崇拜
So thank you very much, it’s rather smart for Me.
很感謝你們，這個很漂亮
Very good.
很好
This time, you know, four forces I have got, luckily.
這次，你知道，我取得四個力量，很幸運
We must give a bandhan to that gentleman.
我們要為這個男士做班丹